Red like a cherry, red like a rose,
Red like the button upon your nose!
Yellow like sunshine, warm and bright,
Yellow like stars in the middle of night!
Blue is the ocean, deep and wide,
Blue is the wave on a splashing ride!
Red, yellow, green, and blue,
A rainbow bridge for me and you!
Mix them up and watch them shine,
Your bright colors, yours and mine!
Green like the grass where the bunnies hop,
Green like a tree all the way to the top!
Orange like a pumpkin round and sweet,
Purple like grapes that are good to eat!
Dip your brush and give a swirl,
Coloring the happy world!
Red, yellow, green, and blue,
A rainbow bridge for me and you!
Mix them up and watch them shine,
Your bright colors, yours and mine!
Paint a rainbow in the sky! So pretty!